hi, everyone. So this syriza videos is going
to be going over a Web framework technology called Django
. So Django is this thing which essentially allows you
to make dynamic websites. Now. What that means
is we could make websites now through Django that will
allow us to store things in a database load pages
dynamically based on what's in the database, and also
do a lot of different cool things in terms of
making an actual living breathing website. In the previous
Siri's, we made static websites using just HTML,
CSS and JavaScript. Those were all front and technologies
that run in the browser. Django is a Web
server built on python, which will be running in
a server and basically handling requests to our website.
So this will make a lot more sense once we
actually get into it. But remember, from our
howto how the Internet works lecture that basically, when
someone goes to a website, it takes the Europa
and basically makes a request to that girl to the
Web server. The Web server is basically, um
, what we're gonna be writing using Django. You
might have heard of some different technologies such as ruby
on rails or maybe no Js those air. Essentially
other Web frameworks for B is ruby on rails is
Britain, and Ruby Note is Britain and JavaScript and
Python is the Web frame where Django is the Web
framework. Python is written, written in Python.
There's also something called Flask, which is essentially a
more lightweight version of it. But Django is the
one I like to use, because once you know
how to use it, it provides a lot of
powerful functionality right out of the box. The thing
is, is that it's actually a little bit of
a challenge to learn if you don't have someone guiding
you through the process. So that's kind of the
goal of these videos for me, because when I
tried to learn Django, it took me basically like
five failed attempts, and I kept trying to learn
and trying to learn it never got it, until
finally someone helped me learn on an internship that I
did. So hopefully through these videos, you'll be
able to get that initial push that you need to
really understand what's going on in order to cheque out
Jango. Just it's spelled like this deejay angio.
If you type it in, then first thing we
get is Django the Web framework for something or the
other perfectionists with the deadline, I would not call
myself a perfectionist, but I do have deadlines.
So this makes sense. Um, as you can
see, it has stuff you can download it.
Love of law. So on. So, yeah
, Next videos, we're gonna be talking about basically
building a website using Django, and we'll be building
a specific type of website, um, to kind
of guide our discussion through the features that Django has
. And the great thing is that once you learn
one web framework like Django, it's then really easy
to learn other ones, like Ruby on Rose or
tto learn no Js or to learn flask. Because
all of those web frameworks all any Web framer really
has, like, a set of specific things that
it has to do a set of core functionalities.
And once you know what those are, you know
what to look for in a new one that you
don't know. So it becomes a lot easier to
pick them. So hopefully, by learning how to
build with Django, you'll actually be well equipped to
do a lot of different things using Web development.