or writing guys get ready for the best Django tutorials
areas in the entire universe. So first things first
. What is Django exactly? Well, it's a
Web application framework built with python on a Framework is
basically a collection of modules. Pre written codes help
with a particular task. On Jang Go's case,
that task is building a Web up. So rather
than creating a full Web application from absolute scratch ourselves
using python trying to reinvent the wheel, we can
instead harness the power of the jungle framework to help
us out with things like user authentication, template in
routing and much, much more. So basically,
my Friends Jungle allows us to easily create dynamic Web
ups using python. Now imagine this scenario. We
have our client eyebrows over here, and we want
to make a request in this browser to a particular
profile page on a Web site. So we got
to my app dot com forward slash profile. Now
this website is be empowered by Django on the servant
. So over here on the service is where Django
is going to do all of its magic and really
help us out. So Jungle receives this request right
here, looks at it and says, Okay,
well, I know that you need to now communicate
with database to grab information for this profile, so
I'll help you do that. Jungle helps us with
this. Then it retrieves that data and says,
Right, What do you want to do with it
? You want to stick it into a hasty Mel
template? No problem. I'll help with that as
well. So it does that and sends that to
the browser to It helps with all of this kind
of service, and magic over here really makes creating
a Web application really simple. All right, And
so throughout this series will be using jungle to create
this block from the ground up. And along the
way, we're gonna learn about a lot of different
things, such as user authentication to implement some kind
of logging sign up system. We'll take a look
at jangle farms as well lost. Lots of other
different things, such as routing the jungle, are
M TEM plating and tonnes more so another good reason
to use Jango is because the jungle documentation is really
, really good. It's seconds it on whenever you
want to search for for example forms. It's gonna
have something to do with that on the documentation,
in fact, loads to do with that so you
can just click on whatever you like. I was
gonna give you loads of different examples and many tutorials
. Almost. Okay, so I would highly employ
you to cheque this out. If you do get
stuck on something, I'll leave the link down below
. Now, as always, are giving you all
of the course files for this Siri's. You can
find them on my Gig Harbour Repo Jungle Playlist.
The link is gonna be down below on DH.
I've doing a different branch for each different lessons.
So if you want to see the code for lesson
five, for example, you need to select the
lesson five brunch and you can find all the cold
inside hit. All right, So just a couple
more things I am gonna be using Atom for this
Siri's. It's a really cool free text editor.
So I employ you to download that as well.
You can find it at atom dot I hope I'm
also gonna be using Cmdr. Or Commander that is
a consul emulator for Windows. You don't have to
use this idea because I think it's quite cool.
But if you prefer to use the default on Windows
one automatic one, that's absolutely fine as well.
Now, because jungle uses python, you will need
python installed on your computer Before you start this.
Siris on DH probably advise you to learn a little
bit about the python basics before you start this Siri's
as well. So if you want to do that
, you want to cheque out my python three tutorial
for beginners. Siri's I'm gonna Leave the Link Down
below. That shows you how to instal Python along
with a lot of the basics of python as well
, and that is going to give you a good
base work for the rest of this series right here
. So now we've got that out of the way
. Let's crack on and start created this block with